<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Wearable Device]]></title>
  <link href="http://me310-ustc-2013.github.io/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://me310-ustc-2013.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2013-11-06T16:38:11+08:00</updated>
  <id>http://me310-ustc-2013.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Liu Mu Shuai(Shawn) Qiu]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thoughts About Task Management Wearable Devices Day Two]]></title>
    <link href="http://me310-ustc-2013.github.io/blog/2013/11/06/thoughts-about-task-management-wearable-devices-day-two/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-06T16:37:00+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://me310-ustc-2013.github.io/blog/2013/11/06/thoughts-about-task-management-wearable-devices-day-two</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I have to be a hard worker those days. I should think what I will do tomorrow,
or I would be caught unprepared when I finished the task at hand, found the
materials was not in hand and ended up with wasting time, especially when I need
to take the boring classes in the school, though I skipped most of them this
term &hellip;</p>

<p>At this time, I am wondering what I should do. So I write those line down.</p>

<p>There always times that I know what I should do &mdash; they flash through my mind
and I do not have the convenient way to store it. I do not want to take out my
smartphone and write them down when walking in the street or brushing my teech
or whatever so.</p>

<p>If at this time, there is a wearable device that is with all the time. I could
just say and record them. Kind of like recording the idea of recording the flash
or writers &mdash; I have need for such moment too. Somethimes I read somethings
really interesting and it let me have some really interesting or important
ideas. At those time, I must remind myself to take out my smartphone and write
some stubs. But it is not convenient. If you have that experience, you will find
out &mdash; it takes some willingness to do such job. Again, if there is a wearable
device that let you conveniently record such flashing ideas, it would be great!</p>

<p>Ok, I will figure out what I should next not!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thoughts About Task Management Wearable Devices Day One]]></title>
    <link href="http://me310-ustc-2013.github.io/blog/2013/11/05/thoughts-about-task-management-wearable-devices-day-one/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-05T08:36:00+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://me310-ustc-2013.github.io/blog/2013/11/05/thoughts-about-task-management-wearable-devices-day-one</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The task management system is what I want the most. The point is the
seamlessness for thinking and recording, then operating in the future. I always
want such a task management system. Current stuffs on smartphone or pc reaaly
does not satisfy me for a really long time.</p>

<p>Every time, things or thoughts just pop up while you are working or thinking. At
that time, I do not want open my evernote on pc or on smartphone, I want to
record what I think of immediately. Here are one scenario:</p>

<ol>
<li><p>Waking up this morning, I want to know whether my credit card support Hong
Kong dollar. At that time my pc or smartphonne are not turned on. And for
such a little task, I do not want to open my smartphone and type this task
in, and of course not pc. I want to just say, find whether my credit card
support Hong Kong dollar or not and it should be put my task pool for being
dealt with in the future.</p></li>
<li><p>I have written an application to record the start time of my current task(and
this app was not intended for such function in the first place I was writting
it ). But I have to press the button manually to record the time. And if the
wearable device could record the start time and end time of the task I am
working just by receiving voice control. I would be much convenient and I
will be hooked by this.
&mdash; For example, I first write this draft reply from 8:00 am to 8:27 am.</p></li>
</ol>


<p>Right now, I am not supposed to write this idea down. But to make sure it get
recorded, I still did that. And I now I forgot what I should do. So the things
&mdash; stack job control system could be in work. I will not bother to even think to
get myself back on track.</p>

<p>This raise the point of the implementation stuff mentioned by Andrew.
Implementation first thinking is really my kind of thinking most time and it is
really helpful for Andrew to clearly point that out. It will help me in the
futher thinking. But just for this point, I do not mean implementation. I will
try get my point through.</p>

<p>Computer is much like human. For exmaple, CPU is similar with the brain of
human. And mouth, eye, nose, hand and etc are the I/O system of human. So the
technology developed for computer could turn back to apply on human being. And
the stack job control system is the most useful, obvious one that I could think.
We are using technology in computer to enhance human&rsquo;s life. So what I really
want to say is not implementation, but what we could learn from the technology
of computer. The case for priority queue is pretty much the same.</p>

<p>I hope I got my idea through. If not, feel free to ask any further questions. It
is not natural to get into this mood of thinking anyway.</p>

<p>As for the platform, Andrew is aiming at something big than what I can think. It
is really hard to build a platform like the Android or iOS. What I mean for
platform is an extension or the first task management system &mdash; the next phase of
work. I am not thinking of a platform for developers. I am thinking to build
convenient wearble device that becomes the information center, communication
center task center and whatever center of futhure people. We are making this
platform. Maybe a goog analogy is an integration of several functions based on
the architecture we build for the task management system. But this idea may not
be better than Andrew&rsquo;s platform.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
